{
    "id": "b1f51a96e9e649de957e912a0aefcd1a",
    "title": "General grammar worksheet (intermediate level)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6c9fa3fc812849708a791804987bbed2",
            "title": "General Grammar Exercise (Intermediate Level)",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I …..................... . yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "went for a walk",
                        "went for walk",
                        "had been going for a walk"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He got angry before I ..................... .. a word.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "said",
                        "had said",
                        "have said"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I ...................... this I shall be wrong.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "did",
                        "will do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said that he ………………… him the day before.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "saw",
                        "had seen",
                        "was seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rita asked ………………….. she could go home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "weather",
                        "whether"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I ………………… to Mumbai I will see him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "went",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ..................... smoking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has left",
                        "has given up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We …………………. playing when it started raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "left",
                        "stopped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He went to America to ……………… English.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "learn",
                        "know"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She knows …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to swim",
                        "how to swim"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}